Episode 93
Three years ago,
I waited for you to return from Elveron
to Sapphire Street
to put a real ring
on my finger.
This time,
it's your turn to wait for me.
Wait for me to return from abroad
and put
this real ring on for me.
Is that okay?
Okay.
Three months later.
Mom,
you have just recovered.
Let me handle things like
carrying the luggage.
You silly girl,
I'm not that fragile.
Noemi,
shouldn't we
tell Mr. Bradley
about our return?
No need.
Once everything is resolved,
I want to give him a surprise.
So, should we
go to the hotel now or...
Let's go to the Curtis family first.
There are some matters
that need to be settled.
Although my daughter
is not married to the Bradley family yet,
Niko
has deep feelings for my daughter.
They will remarry sooner or later.
The Curtis family and the Bradley family
are already one family.
As long as
you provide me with enough benefits,
it will be a piece of cake for you
to work with the Bradley family.
That's right.
You are using
my relationship with the Bradley family to make
money.
You really disgust me.
Who's speaking?